The men holding Bratton
used this boy as a suicide bomber.
I need you to tell me
everything As'ad said to you.
He said that the man who killed
your friends... was another soldier
Collinson. we need to go back!
Just give the order!
Extraction denied.
Have you come to a decision
about our offer to join Section 20
Our own people have got to realise
that they are not a separate entity
from the rest of the people.
We are a free people.
a free nation.
"Don't you realise that the people
of Zimbabwe are a sovereign people."
"We don't have to intervene."
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
We don't have to be
like the British.
And who are they after all?
Our invaders and colonisers
of yesterday.
Prepare for exit.
Fuck!
Go on. bastard. do it.
Job done. Mugabe's dead.
How can you be so sure?
"President Mugabe
was uninjured in the attack.
but one of his body doubles
is reported dead."
"A suspected gunman. Felix Masuku.
was immediately arrested
and two of his accomplices
shot dead."
"The Zimbabwean Intelligence Service
claims that they have evidence
the assassination attempt was
planned by the British government
with the help of the..."
This is becoming a serious problem.
Christ! He's a British soldier.
Was.
Felix Masuku's parents were killed
in 1982 by Mugabe's troops
in the Matabeleland massacres.
He fled Zimbabwe
was brought up by an aunt in Peckham.
At 18. he joined the Royal Engineers.
before returning to Zimbabwe
six years ago.
You're concerned this history
adds credence to Mugabe's claim
that Britain
is behind the assassination? In one.
Could you hold. please.
We need you to resolve this problem.
Hugh. Understood.
So you want me
to break him out of prison? Correct.
Masuku's being held in the secure
wing of Chikurubi Prison in Harare
No guns. no noise.
No footprints back here. This
is a fully deniable operation.
Layla will be your contact
on the ground.
She'll be based in South Africa
until required in Harare.
You'll be travelling in
on a business visa.
This is your identity. Your cover
will be as an illicit diamond deale
John Dean?
Any objections?
Couldn't be James?
The operation codename
is Ugly Trade.
Chikurubi was originally built
as a British fortress.
We can provide you
with early blueprints.
schematics. archive photos.
whatever you might need
to plan the escape.
Be under no illusion. this prison
is Mugabe's most secure facility
and Masuku
will be under close watch.
So how long do I have
to spring Masuku?
His trial is set
for eight weeks from now.
Look. if we can't leave footprints.
why send a Brit?
My point entirely.
You have a problem with this?
If we had no hand
in the assassination.
why are we so concerned
about Masuku?
Isn't just another case
of deny. deny?
Mugabe will use this as a show trial
to destroy the credibility of the UK
across the entire continent.
And. believe me. it's fragile.
Right now. Masuku represents
a threat to the realm.
He cannot be allowed to stand trial
There is one other thing. John.
If this goes wrong...
The last bullet's for me.
Well. let's hope
it doesn't come to that.
John?
I thought you should know.
As'ad's body hasn't been recovered.
John! John. they're leaving him?!
So. he might still be alive?
Well. it's a big desert.
He didn't... tell you anything?
Such as? Anything that might tell u
where he could have gone?
I don't speak Arabic.
Your passport
in the name of John Dean.
Driving licence and condoms.
Standard issue for Africa.
Serviced any other officers recently
Or was I the one
with particularly low self-esteem?
Well. we all have a job to do.
Some are more arduous than others.
Don't get your cock shot off.
I'm really sorry. love.
I can't come up this weekend.
I don't really care
what your excuse is.
you've never been around and I
shouldn't expect you to be now.
Alex. grow up. The world
does not revolve around you.
Why can't you understand that?
Alex?
John. it's me.
Listen. erm... I'm sorry.
It's just she's 17 now.
She's gotta start understanding
what it is I do.
No. no. it's not that.
Erm.... listen. there's something
I've got to tell you.
Just hang on one second.
Two minutes.
Sorry. love.
what was it you wanted to say?
Nothing.
You sure?
Yep. It can wait.
OK. Well. I'll call you
when I get back. I've gotta go. OK?
OK.
"Bye."
Why didn't you tell him?
Felix Masuku. who is also known
as Raymond Frayn.
Irish passport.
South African passport. US passport.
These are all SAS issue IDs. sir.
It gets better. Not only did Masuku
serve in the Regiment between
January 2001 and March 2004.
but since returning to Zimbabwe.
he's been an intelligence source
for MI6.
And we're claiming Masuku
doesn't work for us?!
This isn't just embarrassing.
this... this really stinks.
And?
You knew this. Didn't you?
Have you told Porter?
Porter knows what he needs to know.
Haven't you got a flight to catch.
lieutenant?
This place is dangerous for you.
my friend.
Make sure you behave here otherwise
you will end up in Chikurubi Prison.
If you end up here.
you can kiss your mother goodbye.
You will never see her again.
Harry Curtis. Welcome to Jo'burg.
I like the open air approach
to the embassy. Very un-British.
It made sense
that we met off site.
Hope you're not too knackered. Most
people are undone by the altitude.
I had nose bleeds for a whole month.
Maybe that just happens to
high flyers. Mr First Secretary.
Hardly.
I got everything you asked for.
All legit South African documents.
In the name of a real life
SONOP Inspector. Lizbet Dreyer.
Their brief is counter narcotics
and smuggling.
May I ask what these are for?
I'm a curious sort. you see.
I hadn't noticed.
Thank you. Mr Curtis.
Right.
Normally people try
and short change me.
In this world.
you don't trust anyone. my friend.
Like you said.... trust no-one.
Hands up.
Easy. Take it easy.
Alright!
Take him away.
Hello? Mr Dean's
been picked up as arranged.
When do you intend to visit?
Tomorrow.
So he's on his own
till you get there.
Will he be comfortable? If he keeps
his head down and avoids trouble.
Here... I'm God.
Why are you here?
I made some bad choices.
Didn't we all?
I'm Anthony Silongo.
No!
Argh!
Go!
I've got information. Useful
information. About the assassin.
Lexie.
What information?
I know him. I know who he is.
He'll trust me. I'm British.
My name is Elisabet Dreyer.
Elisabet. Elisabet Dreyer.
You are a despicable man.
You are a despicable man
in an ugly trade.
Ugly. My name is Elisabet Dryer....
Dreyer.
He doesn't trust you. Mr Dean.
And to be honest. I don't blame him.
You've wasted my time.
Sit.
Please.
Wow. I didn't know they allowed
conjugal visits.
Mr John Dean.
Who wants to know?
The South African Government.
We've been monitoring
your smuggling activities.
We believe it's time
you were brought to account.
It was you who had me arrested?
As I will have you extradited
to South Africa to face charges.
Do you have anything to say?
Yeah. darling. get me an upgrade.
Suite. jacuzzi? OK. Mr Dean.
don't get clever with me.
From where I'm standing. you are
a despicable man in an ugly trade.
Listen. sweetheart.
you don't know what ugly is.
I've seen how ugly it can be in here.
Obviously you've come face to face
with it.
Yeah.
I have.
Are you saying you've received
brutal treatment?
No. love. I'm not. I'm saying
everyone is extremely well treated.
Everyone.
Thank you for your assistance.
Colonel. Pleasure to cooperate.
We would appreciate it if Mr Dean
could be moved to a secure wing.
We consider him
to be a dangerous criminal.
and until we have custody of him.
we need to know he's safe.
Of course. And once again.
a pleasure.
Thank you.
You never touch Masuku.
Understand?
Yes. sir.
And if anyone else asks to speak
to Mr Dean. I want to know about it
Yes?
What news of Porter?
He's met the target face to face.
Says he's unharmed.
Masuku's not been tortured?
No. His words were
"extremely well treated."
Really? That may help explain
something. Why?
We intercepted a communication.
They're moving Masuku to
a remand cell under the courthouse.
When?
Noon. the day after tomorrow.
Shit! Have they brought forward
the trial? By two months.
and if they're not torturing Masuku.
they must have the evidence they need
We have accelerate our plans. Well.
I can't just walk back in there.
Tomorrow then?
Porter has to know. Layla.
You've got 48 hours.
I need a copy of an extradition
document now. Where are you?
You know I can't tell you that.
Mr Curtis.
OK. Er. I'll send you
non-specific documentation.
You fill in the blanks.
Who are you?
Friend.
Your cell?
Don't suppose we're off
to breakfast?
Welcome. Mr Dean.
I'm guessing this isn't
Queensberry Rules?
You guess right.
Vincent!
Vincent! Vincent! Vincent!
Bet on me.
I'll give him the first round.
then you can take all the odds
you can get.
What's in it for you?
Keep him... away from that boy.
OK.
We need a handicap.
Ding-ding!
Whoa!
You're not doing so well. my friend.
Double the odds.
I've got the Englishman!
Vincent! Vincent! Vincent!
Quiet!
Alright. boys.
Ding-ding!
Again? So soon?
Consider me your number one stalker.
Mr Dean.
I have your extradition papers.
Time is short.
You need to go through everything
thoroughly.
If there is anything you wish to
appeal. you have until tomorrow n
This is all very sudden.
Deadlines are changing constantly.
Everything you need
is in this document.
I should warn you that if I don't
receive your confirmation signature.
you might remain here indefinitely.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
It's possible.
I can give you my confirmation
signature first thing tomorrow.
Thank you. Mr Dean.
That would be a relief.
You'll need to remember
this case number.
It will help drive through
the paperwork.
Colonel. how fortunate.
I have a copy of Mr Dean's
extradition application for you.
How efficient! Usually I'm sent
this by your Department of Justice.
I was able to expedite things.
So I see.
Land...
Rover...
Under...
Angel.
Land Rover Under Angel.
You asked to see me?
Organise another fight.
Set two men against me.
No one will bet against you.
Except you.
I'll take the first fight.
I'll throw the second.
We'll both do well.
When?
Tomorrow morning. Same time.
first light.
Tshuma.
You have urgent mail from Little Fox.
You're coming with me.
Am I?
Trust me.
Hello.
Keys.
Where the fuck is everyone?
Cock fight.
Let's go.
There's been a breach.
I've been compromised.
Get out. Head for the RV.
What about Porter?
He needs transport. I can still get
there. Look after yourself. Get out.
That's an order!
Let's go.
Isn't this a dead end?
Yup. but this is our way out.
What?
OK. go on.
Stop.
Go back.
Give me a hand.
One. two. three.
OK. go.
Go.
You're in charge.
Where the fuck are we?
Old munition tunnels.
Left or right?
Oh. fuck!
Down.
Where's the fucking Land Rover?
I don't fucking believe it!
Go. go!
Hurry up!
Yes!
Get in!
Go! Go!
Radio traffic confirms there has
been a break-out from Chikurubi.
Local police have been ordered
to set up road blocks.
Oh. size 10. Result!
Shit!
Do you think he saw us?
What are we doing?
Ditching this piece of shit.
Cut some brush.
we need to hide the car.
So you want me
to break him out of prison.
Masuku has to disappear completely.
Understood?
Sir.
Of course.
Drop the knife.
I said drop it.
Before you do this....
you should know something.
I was set up.
The whole assassination was a trap.
They were waiting for me.
On your knees.
I don't make mistakes. Dean.
I'm ex-Regiment. just like you.
Yeah. I was hired by British
Intelligence to kill Mugabe.
Someone betrayed me.
I said get on your knees!
They betrayed me!
They betrayed you. too!
Where was the Land Rover. Dean?
No. where was it?
Shut up! It was supposed to be
there. wasn't it?
Think. Dean! Think!
Those weren't prison guards outside
the prison. they were Elite Guards.
What. ten seconds after the alarm
went off they were outside?
Tshuma's men. Dean.
The same men who captured me.
Who do you trust?
Who the fuck do you trust?
My name's Porter.
Sync by georgel24
for www.addic7ed.com
IMS Subtitles
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org